http://www.fineoperaglasses.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Articles
Opera Glasses Styles - Which is Right for You?Opera Glasses vs BinocularsOpera Glasses- A Closer LookOpera Glasses: 5 Things to know before you buyThe History of Opera Glasses and Theater BinocularsReasons to Use Opera Glasses or Opera BincoularsAttending a Performance: 5 ways to make it UnforgettableThe History of OperaWhy Would I Ever Need Opera Glasses or Theater Binoculars?Review: Wicked the Musical with Opera GlassesA Review of Shear Madness the Comedic Mystery with Opera GlassesHow the Theater Affects Us TodayMadame Butterfly, the Betrayal: A Review of the OperaOpera Glasses, Love, Racism, and Hairspray: A ReviewPast and Present, Everyone Loves the TheaterThe Phantom of the Opera: A Review with Opera Glasses
FREE SHIPPING!!!
Shop by Style
Traditional Opera Glasses
With Lorgnette Handle
With Chain
With Reading Light
4x Magnification
Sport Binoculars
All Styles
Privacy Policy
Peace of Mind.
When it comes to shopping online, what could be more important?
Privacy Statement
At Fine Opera Glasses.com we understand how important it is to keep your personal information secure; especially credit card information.  We have taken steps to ensure that your privacy will not be compromised.  If you have questions or concerns that are not answered, feel free to contact us during normal business hours by calling our Customer Service line 801.613.0002.  Send us an email 24/7 by clicking here.
Information we do not collectOur web server does not automatically recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address.  LIkewise, our server does not retain your credit card information; not even the last four digits. The only time we ever see any of your credit card data is if we input the order for you.  But,as soon as we click the 'Add' button, the data disappear forever.
We hold all personal information in strict confidence and it always remains a perfect mystery to us. As a matter of fact, we wouldn't even know where to find it.
Information that may be collectedWe have access to and may retain the e-mail address of those who communicate with us via e-mail or input the email address as part of the order.  We may also collect information volunteered by customers, such as survey information and/or site registration.
Google, Bing, Yahoo and other major search engines may aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, time spent on the site, search keywords used, etc.  FineOperaGlasses.com, like all top ecommerce sites, uses this information to improve the content of our web pages and customize content and layout for the benefit of the shopper.  No personal information is ever accessible.
We hate spamJust like you, we find it very annoying and an unwelcome intrusion. We will not use your email address inappropriately.  If you do not want to receive e-mail or other possible contact from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail, calling or writing, and telling us that you do not want to receive such contact from our company.
Terms of Use StatementYou understand and agree that the owners of this site shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, data or other intangible losses (even if the owners of this site have been advised of the possibility of such damages), resulting from the use or the inability to use the product(s) and or service(s) or any misuse of the product(s) and or service(s) in a manner not in accordance with their intended use.
To sum it all up--When you purchase your opera glasses from FineOperaGlasses.com, you can rest assured that your personal information is safe.
Home | Shop by Style | Shop by Color | Shop by Price | About Us | Contact Us | Privacy | Dealers | Wholesale | Shipping | Antique Opera Glasses
Copyright 2020, Aria, LLC 2130 Valley View Drive Layton, UT 84040 Support@FineOperaGlasses.com
